Two agents. One city. No merci.
From Paris with Love is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Pierre Morel.
James Reese has a good job as an ambassador's aid in France, but his real
passion is a side gig—working in a minor role in the CIA.
He would love to be a full-fledged agent and can't believe his
luck when he lands an assignment with Charlie Wax.
Trigger-happy Charlie soon has James crying for his desk job, but when he learns that the same guys they're
trying to catch are after him, James realises that Charlie may be his only hope of survival.
Charlie Wax, played by John Travolta.
James Reece, played by Jonathan Rhys Meyers.
Caroline, played by Kasia Smutniak.
Ambassador Bennington, played by Richard Durden.
M. Wong, played by Bing Yin.
Nichole, played by Amber Rose Revah.
From Paris with Love is a 2010 French action-thriller film directed by Pierre
Morel and starring John Travolta and Jonathan Rhys Meyers.
The screenplay was co-written by Luc Besson.
The film was released in the United States on February 5, 2010, by Lionsgate
Films and both in the United Kingdom and Japan by Warner Bros.
The film explores themes of central intelligence agency (cia),
ambassador, paris, france, undercover, explosive.
The tone is intense.